<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lacework Cloud Security for your AWS Environments on AWS Immersion Day with Lacework</title>
    <link>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lacework Cloud Security for your AWS Environments on AWS Immersion Day with Lacework</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lacework Global Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/31_global_dashboard.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/31_global_dashboard.html</guid>
      <description>The Global Dashboard displays a visual summary of the following items:
 All CloudTrail, network, user, and process events ingested by Lacework Entity behaviors identified by Lacework Events and critical events generated by Lacework   You can filter on a timeframe using the Last … drop-down located in the upper right corner. You can filter from the last 24 hours to 90 days (or 180 days if you have subscribed for additional storage).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lacework Global Search</title>
      <link>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/32_global_search.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/32_global_search.html</guid>
      <description>Lacework’s global search provides the ability to search across a number of assets in Lacework as shown in the figure below. To start a search, click Search and enter text in the search bar and Lacework immediately returns results when the search finds any assets that match the entered string, within the following time constraints:
 Events created in the last 90 days Networks accessed in the last 7 days All other assets created or accessed in the last 30 days   Click on the Search in the top left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Compliance</title>
      <link>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/33_aws_compliance.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/33_aws_compliance.html</guid>
      <description>Lacework’s AWS security platform automatically validates all configurations against the controls established as best practices for securing your cloud environment. Our interactive reports deliver insights into “passed or failed” controls with recommendations on how to fix out-of-compliance configuration components.
 Navigate to the Compliance Dashboard page in the Lacework Console, select Compliance &amp;gt; AWS &amp;gt; Dashboard. This dashboard provides a view of your AWS accounts that are integrated with Lacework and their related compliance information and details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Container and Host Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/34_container_vulnerabilities.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/34_container_vulnerabilities.html</guid>
      <description>Lacework provides the ability to assess, identify, and report vulnerabilities found on hosts, containers, registries and pods within your environment. This means you can identify and take action on software vulnerabilities in your environment and manage that risk proactively.
Lacework continuously assesses vulnerability risks, identifies OS packages, and correlates them with publicly known vulnerabilities with risk ratings by severity and CVSS scores.
In this section, we will explore container vulnerabilities. Lacework several types of container/image scanning as well as providing runtime protection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/35_resources.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/35_resources.html</guid>
      <description>The Lacework Console provides visibility into AWS resources that are integrated with Lacework. A resource can be any entity within the cloud deployment, such as an S3 bucket, security group, or EC2 instance. The Resource Inventory page allows you to view and monitor in-use AWS resources’ risk, compliance, and configuration changes and provides visibility for team members with limited or no access to the AWS Management Console. Because Lacework takes regular snapshots of your resources, you can track their changes (diffs) through the Lacework Console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policies</title>
      <link>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/36_policies.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/36_policies.html</guid>
      <description>Lacework policies provide a framework for validating configuration and behavior in your cloud environment. Lacework provides a set of predefined default policies that are visible from the Lacework Console. You can use the default policies to suppress the generation of unwanted alerts in your environment. Default policy IDs start with the LW_ prefix. You may want to create custom policies that check for unwanted behavior in your environment such as Telnet being used in your environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alert Channels and Rules</title>
      <link>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/37_alert_channels_rules.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jefferyfry.github.io/aws-immersion-day-with-lacework/3_lacework_aws_overview/37_alert_channels_rules.html</guid>
      <description>Lacework combines alert channels and alert rules to provide a flexible method for routing alerts. For alert channels (outgoing integrations), you define information about where to send alerts, such as to Jira or Slack. For alert rules, you define information about which alert types to send, such as critical and high severity compliance alerts. This two-part method provides the flexibility to define multiple channels and multiple rules and then have each rule use the channels you specify.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
